friends this is so weird
i hope i'm recording right now
it's really interesting
this is eya and it is um
it is the first of march 2021.
and i literally was talking i pressed
the go live button on stream yard
and
after doing that introduction
and saying a prayer i looked up and it
says that we were not live
this is the second time that it's
happened and i know that i pressed it so
i appreciate your prayers i think this
content today is really important
we're talking about debunking the bible
changes
now it's kind of a play on the words
if you will
because what i'm going to do today is
take a look at
several scripture verses i've taken
screenshots of my king james bible
and we're going to take a look at those
together
now
i am
doing this video i felt called to do it
because there were those no names came
out
and did a video
to debunk
the bible changes
or the mandela effect
and
i listened for a few minutes
and i was aghast because once again they
bring up the lion and the lamb
now for those of you who may not know
is there two instances now in scripture
where the lion has changed to the wolf
in isaiah and the most prominent one
that everybody knows is isaiah 11
6. and in that verse
the lion shall
um
the lion shall lay with the lamb is now
the wolf shall dwell with the lamb it's
different
and it means something totally different
but that being said everyone likes to
quote that especi i would say everyone
quotes that those who see the changes
and those who don't see the changes
and those who don't see the changes will
just rely will say
i don't believe the bible is changing
because the wolf has always been there
and they only refer to that one change
instead of opening up the bible and
letting the bible
speak
what do i mean by that literally going
through and showing scripture
and going through it together
so i
felt led today to go ahead and do that
with you
and we're going to take a look at
several
screenshots i've taken
of my own king james bible some of them
are from online but most of them are
from
one or more of my king james bibles
and of course as always i encourage you
to take out your own bible and look for
yourself in your own bible because every
bible is changing in every language
across the earth some change a little
bit differently some are a little bit
slower
so might not be changed today in this
moment when you open it up but tomorrow
when you go look it will be changed i
know it's totally weird i get it it
sounds
it is unbelievable but wasn't also the
parting of the red sea
was in the miraculous healings in
scripture
and you can go on and on in the book of
exodus you see supernatural things
happen left right and center
god is the same god yesterday today and
tomorrow
forever
he is the god of miracles and miracles
now that's interesting i say that
because i believe what we're seeing
right now are lying signs and wonders
and the lying signs and wonders does not
come from god it comes from the
antichrist
and why do i think these are not just
miracles coming from the lord because we
know it's impossible for god to lie
and the bible is now filled with lies
and confusion and double speak and
grammar errors and nonsense verses and
again if you are not away to this yet
please
i beseech you
with all humility
and love is to stick around
and have the courage
to examine these scripture verses with
us
and i would love to hear your thoughts
in the in the in the live chat
and also in the comments below after the
show goes um when the show is completed
because
i have questions
about what i'm going to show you this is
just a fraction
of changes because
we're seeing changes literally on every
page of the bible
literally from genesis 1 1. i should say
even before that
in the preface of the bible there's now
an
insert about queen elizabeth
but genesis when one is changed and then
the last verse of the bible has changed
and last page in my one of a couple of
my king james bibles now says the end
if you can believe that and then beyond
that are maps most of us have maps in
the back of our bible
they've changed
and the concordance in the back of our
bibles have changed
it is absolutely crazy and yet we can
still find residual
in some of our concordances in the back
of our bible what do i mean
we like the word wine skins
so some of us have wine skins in our
concordance in the back of our bibles
with related scripture verses and when
you go there
they bit the word is erased
it's now changed to bottles
but anyway so i thought you know
enough of referring to isaiah 11 6 as if
that change wasn't enough
but i think it's really important
that when someone is trying to debunk
scripture
changes
that they open up the bible
and either follow along or have a
conversation about them
and
for for those of us who see the changes
what we're experiencing is when we take
the like the following verses i'm going
to share with you
oftentimes the response is not a
dialogue
it's where a person who can't
accept the bible changes will literally
ignore
what we're asking and shut down
and not want to talk about it well
explain to me how that could be possible
if you love the lord
and if you if you are adamant the bible
is not changed
why are you referring why are you
why do you refuse
to talk about
scripture
right
if you don't see the bible changes and
if we come to you with scripture changes
why don't you want to dialogue about it
and i ask that question because it's
almost universal
in almost five years of having my
youtube channel and talking to people
that see the changes and are
experiencing the same responses
i want to know why
people who don't see the changes shut
down
when we bring to them scripture verses
because if you think the bible has not
changed then you should have an
explanation
for what is shared with you
right you need to be a berean
so um
that's what i'm asking so i even before
i i'm i'm really
want to get into this and so what i'm
going to do is say a quick prayer which
i've already prayed first as you know
but then i wasn't live so father in
jesus name be with us right now
and we come to you lord with hearts that
are heavy and
hearts that are yearning for your truth
to be revealed to us
and to those who are seeking truth lord
i pray right now that you be with me
right now lord as you're
you've laid it on my heart to do this
broadcast lord and to show these
scripture verses i pray that those who
are listening right now will literally
have the veil taken from them the veil
of deception and i pray they would see
clearly
what the scriptures teaching right now
and i pray for the courage for everyone
who's listening including myself to
stand firm and to be uncompromising
in what we're seeing happen to the bible
it's inexplainable
but it's undeniable lord that the bible
is under siege and i pray that right now
that the word would go forth the true
words the eternal words
of scripture would go forth
and that people will be reminded of what
the bible once said lord
but be with us right now lord may you
encourage the faint-hearted who are
listening right now and those who are
troubled those who are laden with with
the trials and tribulations in the in
the present moment i pray that you would
lift the burdens that they carry and i
pray that you would support them and
carry them through this hour of testing
and i pray god that you will really help
us to be more like you
to walk in the grace and the humility
that defines you
and help us to be absolutely
resolute
in our faith in our
in our declaration
of
of the truth found in jesus christ the
king of kings and lord of lords you are
absolutely wonderful and um
without you lord we can do nothing so
praise the lord we give you all the
glory in jesus name
so friends i'm just going to say hi to
people in the chat and i just want to
dive into the content because there's a
lot for me to go through i would
appreciate your prayers as i go through
this information i mean just pray in the
spirit because
i have a lot i want to go through and i
want answers i want
people
who are trying to debunk the bible
changes
to make their opinion known in live chat
or in the comments below
i want people to respond
to these verses
i think it's important
because all too often what we're seeing
is
those who deny the changes don't want to
talk about
other changes other than the wine skins
or the lion
it's like it's either the bottles that
they want to talk about or the lion but
they don't want to talk about the
nonsense verses and the grammar errors
the doctrinal errors and and everything
out the new words in the bible words
that are erased like discernment and
demons and
lawlessness and trials and tribulations
and jubilee
and even messiah messiah has been erased
from the new testament
it's crazy
messiah is now only found twice
in the old testament
the king james bible it's crazy
so let's go ahead and dive into this
i'm glad you guys are here today but
just bear with me
yeah
okay let's go and take a look here so
i'm glad you guys are all here right now
god bless you all let's go ahead and
take a look at these scripture verses
and again friends i do appreciate
prayers as i go through this because
it's a lot and friends i'll tell you
what i did i literally have thousands of
screenshots and so what i did today is i
just went through and i just picked a
few of them
right i just picked a few but there's so
many
others
and um so i'm just literally going to go
through these these
these screenshots here with you i have a
lot so you need to bear with me it's
going to be a lot of content but you
know what
again i want to know what the what
what those who demon are trying to
debunk the bible changes tell me what
these verses mean
so let's get started and i'm not
actually asking you hold on a minute
hold on
sorry about that friends because of my
um cold and yes i have a cold i don't
have covet but um
it just kind of catches me unaware
sometimes so that's why you have to bear
with me if i have to pause myself and
take some tea or
or
take care of matters in my cold okay
so what i'm going to do is literally
going to go through this together and
just bear with me and i want to have
some dialogue about what you guys think
about this
and again i'm some of this i'm going to
breathe really quickly some scripture
versus i'm going to go ahead and talk
about it but really we're just going to
take a quick look see here what this
says here
this is actually in um
ii timothy 3 and i apologize that it's
not on here
but um
sorry you guys with my voice
but um this is second timothy 3 and it
says this know also the last days
perilous times shall come for men shall
be lovers of their own selves
covetous boasters proud
blasphemers disobedient to parents
unthankful unholy
without natural affection truce breakers
false accusers incontinent
fierce despisers of those that are good
traitors heady high-minded lovers of
pleasure more than the lovers of god
and then it goes on saying four of the
swords are they which creep into houses
and lead captive silly women laden with
sins led away with divers lusts
ever learning blah blah
here the issue here is that there's a
lot of new words here in this verse
what what does it mean to be
for example incontinent right what does
that mean to be incontinent you know
incontinent is an end time sign
or being fierce isn't on
an end times an end time sign
traitors and heady and high-minded never
heard of such a thing i never knew those
words
were end time signs but now they are
a lot that's highlighted here is
unfamiliar to me
and i would love people who are denying
the changes to explain
what this means i mean
incontinent
i mean that one just stands out like a
red flag but all these words are foreign
bottles of water we have bottles of
water now in the bible
we have bottles of wine bottles of milk
and bottles of water
well when we take a look at the verses
now this is just a from online bible
because i wanted to make sure i
captivated all three instances
but like in genesis 21 14 it doesn't
even make sense
and abraham rose up early in the morning
and took bread and
a bottle of water and gave it to hagar
and by the way did you know that abraham
and hagar are now married
in the bible
yes married
let me continue
took a bottle of water and gave it to
hagar and putting it
the bottle of water on her shoulder only
one
and the child so she has on her shoulder
on her one shoulder she has a bottle of
water and a child
and send her away
how does a bottle of water stay on her
shoulder
right
let alone a child how does a child stay
on her shoulder
it doesn't even make sense
genesis 21 15 and the water was spent in
the bottle
did you know the water was spent in the
bottle
and she cashed she threw the child under
one of the shrubs
do you remember that
the water was spent in the bible and she
cast the child
under one of the shrubs
and genesis 21 19 and god opened her
eyes and she saw a well of water and she
went
and filled the bottle with water
and gave the lad drink that's right a
lad we have lads in the bible now
bottle of water
it's craziness
we now have the lord hissing in the
bible
does that sound like your god in isaiah
11 um let's see what it is isaiah 7 18
and it shall come to pass in that day
let me make sure it's still recording
i think it is
and it shall come to pass in that day
that the lord shall
hiss for the fly
and then it even says and for the be so
now the lord is hissing for a fly and a
bee
does that sound like you're god or does
that sound like the serpent
does your lord hiss
i really know the serpent
and i know serpents like insects
like flies and
bees
but now the lord is hissing in the bible
huge change
i don't know
this lord that they speak of and i don't
want to know him
this is isaiah 27 12 and it shall come
to pass in that day
that the lord shall beat off
from the channel
and by the way
we have channel that's right like a
youtube channel
in the bible one time in this verse
we have the word channel
subscribe
and media and publish
are in the bible now
as well
but this verse says and it shall come to
pass that the lord shall beat off
can you picture that
do you want to picture that
are you troubled by picturing that
exactly
there are no words
to describe what we're seeing in the
bible
but blasphemous
this one literally i've shared this so
many times this one
this one change right here caused me to
fall on the ground
and weep
her
i wept so loudly in a fetal position
unto the lord
this verse right here in luke 135 is now
calling
the creator
that holy thing
luke 1 35 now says this today
and the angel answered and said unto her
the holy ghost should be the holy spirit
shall come upon thee
and the power of the heist
that is capitalized
i've never known god's title to be
called highest
what about you
and the power of the highest
shall overshadow thee
do you remember the word overshadow
yeah neither do i overshadow thee
therefore also
that holy thing
which shall be born of thee
shall be called the son of god
is that what you call jesus
that holy thing
[Music]
have you ever called him that
i hope not
when i talk about the scripture changes
demoting jesus
this is one of them
and it's disgusting
habakkuk 2 16 now says this
thou art filled with shame for glory
drink thou also and let thy foreskin be
uncovered
the cup of the lord's right hand
shall be turned unto thee and
shameful
spewing
shall be on thy glory
do you remember that
can
you tell me what this means
anyone
anyone at all
does anyone else have a problem with
this
unrecognizable language in scripture
unrecognizable imagery in the bible
unrecognizable slang in the bible
unrecognizable words
we now have worlds
did you know that
worlds
we have worlds in the planet in the
bible now we have planets
we have aliens
we have saturn and mars and jupiter
but check this out
it now says that the lord made worlds in
hebrews 1 2 and hebrews 11 3. now of
course we know the mormons love this
and of course we know the mormons are
deceived are in a cult
but this verse right here says that god
made the worlds
half in these last days spoken unto us
by his
son and notice that his
is not capitalized
whom he hath appointed heir of all
things by whom also he made the worlds
hebrews 11 3 through faith we understand
the worlds
were framed framed
i remember created
not
framed by the word of god no he wasn't
framed by the word of god
but that's what it says framed by the
word of god you know john 1 1 says
in the beginning was the word and the
word was with god and the word was god
jesus christ is the word of god
but anyway
worlds is new in scripture
and here it is
buttocks
buttocks are now in the bible
we have buttocks and bullocks
in the bible now
buttocks
and bullocks
and i might just go ahead and tell you
now
that even the word penis and testicles
are now in some translations of
scripture
but this verse is really ridiculous
this is what it says go look in your own
bible
wherefore hannah took david's servants
and shaved them
and cut their garments
in the midst hard
by their buttocks
and sent them away
is that language that you know
are you shocked
with this
did you memorize the scripture verse
in
matthew which is now called the gospel
according to saint matthew it's a new
title
to
the gospel of matthew it's now called
saint matthew
we now see that jesus christ no longer
comes from the tribe of judah judah
the line of judah
he comes from the line of judas did you
know that
this is a huge doctrinal change
and if you look now in the generation of
jesus christ
you're going to see all types of new
names
and language
revelations 1 13 now says this today and
in the midst of the seven candlesticks
should be lamb stands one like unto the
son of man
and notice that it's not even
capitalized should be some god
jesus is now called the son of man in
the bible
and now
it's crazy
clothed with a garment down to the foot
and gert
about the paps which means
men's breasts or men's nipples in the
strong concordance with a golden girdle
so now jesus has
breasts
and is wearing a
garment down to the foot like a dress
and wearing a golden girdle
men are now wearing
skirts in the bible and purses and hosen
and
leather girdles and lace girdles and
skin girdles and needles of girdles of
needlework
in the bible and bonnets
there's a transgender
homosexual agenda as a rewriting
scripture
second kings 18 now has some new words
in here
and new language like syrian language
and jews language
and new words i have
names of people in cities
that now have dashes in them
in my bibles
grammar errors like in verse 27 of
second kings 18 are on every page my
bible
question mark and then a small
next letter should be capitalized
and i have italicized words now in my
bibles
this verse now says
hath he not sent me to the men which sit
on the wall
that they
may eat their own dung
and drink
their own
piss
with you
does anyone have a problem with this
i do
is this familiar language with you
can you explain the grammar errors
in this verse and the act of
eating
dung
another word for
you know defecation
and drinking piss
do you remember the word piss in the
bible sounds like hiss
piss and hiss
i i just really have no words it leaves
me speechless when i read these
scripture verses
and it's so obviously changed
galatians 4 this is supposedly paul who
used to write
used to have written
most of the
new testament but now we see that
there are other people that are now
writing different epistles in scripture
i've shared them with you before i have
the names of new authors
in one of my 1958 authorized kingdoms
bibles it now says that
different people wrote
the epistles
than paul
but anyway this verse right now here is
a is a whopper of a change
let's take a look galatians 4.
this is supposedly paul speaking
and my temptation which was in my flesh
ye despise not
nor rejected but received me
as an angel of god
even
as christ
jesus
do you remember paul
ever saying that
where is then the blessedness you spake
of
for i bear you record
that if it had been possible
you would have plucked out your own eyes
and have given them
to me
do you remember paul speaking like this
and asking people to
pluck out their own eyes
it's deeply
deeply troubling what we're seeing here
but especially here where now paul is
saying
that they received him as christ jesus
this is in galatians 4.
job job 25 verse 4
and 6 is what i want to look at in this
in this
passage
and even in verse 3 we see
[Music]
a grammar error
but verse 4 says how then can man be
justified with god
and then a small
o for or
how can he be clean
that is born of a woman
and then verse 6 says
how much less man that is a worm
question mark in the small a and the son
of man referring to jesus
which
is
italics is a worm
so now the son of god in scripture is a
worm
i'm letting the scriptures speak for
themselves friends
and that's what it says right here
and the grammar errors
are self-evident
the foreign words
the nonsense verses are self-evident
job
22 verse 24
now describes a man and yes in context
go look
his breasts
are full
of milk
a transgender agenda
in the bible
second samuel 10
verse 4 oh this is it i did take a
picture of this take a look just so you
can see this my own bible let me see
hold on
isn't that interesting it's hold on
friends let's see if i can do this
okay
okay so now it's it's freezing that's
interesting isn't it
i think so
now let's open this up again
here it is
this is in my own bible the one about
the buttocks
just so you can see it oh this is
another one
is that right this is second samuel 10
verse 4.
wherefore hannah took david's servants
and shaved off the one half
of their beard only one half
not all the beer just one half literally
one half
and cut off their garments in the middle
even to their buttocks and sent them
away
so what they did is they caused them to
run naked
in the streets
job 37
verses 22 through
says this today in the king james bible
fair weather cometh out of the north
with god is
terrible
majesty
remember awesome
i've never ever ever
ever heard a song of him talking about
how terrible god is
you know you've heard the song how great
thou art i've never heard how terrible
thou art
have you
god is terrible majesty
i know one who is terrible
majesty and that's
the wicked one
right
the one who's pretending
to be god
the one who will come and deceive many
that he is god and deceive many there
will be a great falling away because
people will believe that the antichrist
is god
anyway that's job 37 verse 22 verse 23
now says this touching
that's right
touching the almighty
touching the almighty and touching is
now italicized
touching
is a new word it's a multiplied word in
scripture
and i've done
videos about this in the past but now
it's erased on my channel i have to
upload my old ones
but if you look up the words with
touching
in them now
many of them
are really perverse
jesus is now
touching
infants in the bible
and his disciples
rebuked them
infants is new in the bible that word
jesus blessed the children
he wasn't touching
infants
but now he is
but just like this verse touching the
almighty
we cannot find him out
he is excellent in power and in judgment
and judgment is missing an e
and in plenty of justice he will not
afflict
men do therefore fear him he respecteth
not any
that are wise
of heart
does that sound like the god that you
know
god is wisdom
why would god have no respect
for those who are wise in heart
it's a new it's a new they change this
verse
but may i remind you
we're always told that god is no
respecter of persons
but now this verse is making it seem
that god
respecteth only
the evil
in heart the stupid in heart
the ungodly and the wicked do you see
some of these changes
one you need to actually picture in your
mind what's being said because that's
comprehension
so then you know you can't put a bottle
of water
and a child on one shoulder
it's impossible
or that you know i mean i can tell you
so many examples
but here it is saying that he respecteth
not any
that are wise of heart
that's a lie
there are a lot of lies now
in scripture
and we know who the father of lies is
and it's not the creator of the heavens
and the earth
it's the god of this
wicked
satanic world
i better make sure you guys are still
with me
let's see here yep you guys are still
with me sorry i'm not oh let me do
something you guys i realize i want to
go and share everything and i hope you
guys are seeing these changes
and i apologize for not making it
completely enlarged here but
this is song of solomon
chapter five
this is what it says today
my beloved
put his hand
by the whole
of the door
and my bowels
were moved for him
do you remember that
is that familiar to you
i don't recognize this at all
it's completely foreign
and it's ridiculous
i mean when i first read this somebody
pointed it out in a live chat
a few years ago and it was just
horrifying my beloved put his hand
by the hole of the door
and her bowels
were moved
for him
does that sound romantic
yeah
no there's a filth
there's a
a horrendous
stench
coming through scripture
the smell of sulfur you know what i'm
saying the smell of wickedness
song of solomon was a beautiful
i mean really all of scripture was so
harmonious and beautiful right
not that there was not sin described in
scripture because there was of course
there was
but not what the language is in there
now
not with the words of bastards and
pissing and eating dung and putting dung
on faces and
um
you know streakers in the bible and
all types of things are in the bible
that were never there before i have to
continue because i'm going off tangent
but this verse is unrecognizable again
those of you who say that the bible
hasn't been changed i need you
to literally
tell me
what these verses
are saying
and put it
in the video description i mean put it
in a comment below
when we approach you those who say the
bible hasn't changed
with these verses
we want you to answer
what this means
that's important
because
we know
you really can't give an adequate answer
we're quite confident of that
and you know it too
how can you not
isaiah 8
has grammar errors in it and spelling
errors like mount zion
and verse isaiah 8 verse 18 is now small
but then we have in verse 19 a really
strange verse and when they shall say
unto you seek unto them that have
familiar spirits and unto
wizards that peep
and that mutter
should not a people seek unto their god
and a question mark of small f for the
living to the dead
unrecognizable
and this even says and they shall pass
through it hardly be stead and hungry
bested
and it shall come to pass that when they
shall be hungry they shall fret
themselves and curse their king and
their god
do you remember that
cursing god
hosea 11 verse 1.
does this mean
this is a
this is a whopper
i drew them with cords of a man
with bands of love
and i was to them as they
that take off the yoke
on their jaws
and i laid
meat
unto them
can anyone even tell me what this means
it's not an issue
of needing a scholar
to tell me what this means
the bible
was known for being written at a level
that a fifth grader could read and
understand
but what we're seeing with these
nonsense verses is just that
a filth a nonsense homosexual innuendos
sexual innuendos
perverse innuendos
they're just no words
judges 11 this is a whopper hold on to
your seats judges 11 now says this
and it came to pass when he saw her
that he rent his clothes and said alas
my daughter
grammar heir with a small t
thou hast brought me very low
and now are one of them that trouble me
for i have opened my mouth unto the lord
and i cannot go back
and she said unto him my father
if thou has opened thy mouth unto the
lord
do to me according to that
which hath proceeded
out of thy mouth
for as much as the lord hath taken
vengeance for thee of thine enemies even
of the children of ammon
and she said unto her father
let this thing be done for me
let me alone
two months
that i may go up
and down
upon the mountains
and bewail my virginity
i and my fellows
and he said go
and he sent her away for two months
and she went with her companions and
bewailed
her virginity upon the mountains
going up
and down upon the mountains
be wailing her virginity
virgin has been multiplied in the bible
no doubt about it they're even calling
one's virginity a flower in the bible
and menstruation as well menstruation is
called a flower
in the bible
it's crazy
what is this
john 1 29 now says this the next day
john seeth
jesus coming unto him
again language it's
not right for me
jesus coming unto him and say behold the
lamb of god which taketh away the sin of
the world only one sin
only one
not plural he only takes away now one
sin
what could that one sin be
anyone
does anybody know what the one sin is
that jesus takes away
anyone
this this was obviously plural sins
because the world doesn't have one sin
it has many sins that jesus christ died
for
right
genesis 45 now says this and he fell
upon his brother
benjamin's neck
and wept
and benjamin
wept upon his neck
we see a lot of repeated
phrases in the bible even in one verse
this is one example of it
there's so many of
them nonsense
genesis 46
says now all the souls
that came with jacob into egypt which
came out of his
loins
so now men
are producing souls
out of their loins
it's not even possible
genesis 49 14 issachar is a strong ass
couching down between
two burdens
he's a strong
ass couching
down between two persons
nonsense verse
so strong ass
and ass couching dumbass
are now in the bible he asses and she
asses and
lighted her ass are now expressions in
the bible
exodus 36 or 7 for the stuff
they had was sufficient
for all the work to make it
and too much
does that even make sense
no
stuff
i mean seriously when i first heard that
stuff was in the bible i laughed
the word was either possessions or
belongings
provision
not stuff
so stuff is throughout scripture now
leviticus 7 9 says this and all the meat
offering that is bacon in the oven
and all that is dressed
in the frying pan one word and in the
pan shall be the priests that offer it
bacon in the oven
and dressed in the frying pan
mark 9 49 says this disgusting thing
for everyone
everyone
shall be salted with fire
and every sacrifice shall be salted
with salt
like cannibalism
roasting human flesh
and yes that's in the bible now roasting
flesh
and the concordance defines flesh
as humans
i've shared this in videos before
and you can go look yourself
this is a big one big change this is in
first john 1 6 it now says this today
if we say that we have fellowship with
him and walk in darkness
we lie and do not
the truth
what does that even mean we do not the
truth the word was practice
or or
love the truth
i go back and forth on this one
and do not the truth
if we say that we have fellowship with
him and walk in darkness we lie
and do not it was love and do not love
the truth
they erase the word love
they also erase the word love in first
corinthians 13 is now called the charity
chapter
it used to be called the love chapter
and now charity
now covers a multitude of sins in the
bible
it used to be love
it still is love for me
love covers a multitude of sins
this verse is missing a word
and it's not just this particular bible
because as i said you should be opening
up your own bibles and looking in your
own king james bible
because the change is there
through this wicked nefarious black
magic they're employing
and that is actually all the ones i'm
going to share with you today
i have
thousands of other screenshots
of changes but the ones that i shared
with you today i think
encompass nonsense versus
grammar errors doctrinal errors
copy and paste jobs
omission of words words added
new names in the bible
i want to hear
how the changes to scripture
can be debunked
because the bible was
perfect
you know
it didn't have grammar errors in it it
didn't have spelling errors in it
and every verse had meaning and now when
you read it you're left scratching your
head like what did i just read and you
have to go reread it again and again and
even if you read it a fourth time
you may not understand it because it's
gibberish
which is
intended
right
the god of confusion
messing with scripture
thinking that he can
erase the word of god
he's such a little
god you know what i mean
he's just
so
stupid
because the word of god endures forever
no matter what they do to the bible
jesus christ exists
apart
from scripture
jesus christ
is not a book
he's not an audiophile he's not a
digital file
he's not a picture
he's not an idol
jesus christ
is the word of god and he endures
forever
which reminds me of something i was
thinking about today and that is
do people who don't see the changes to
scripture
is it possible for people
who don't see the scripture changes
to be born again
and you know what i'm going to say is
jesus christ is the son of god and if
they've made that profession of faith
that is what saves them right you know
what i mean that that faith that jesus
is the christ the son of god you know
believes in the gospel
but i would say that those who say that
they're born again
and you know that they confess jesus
christ as lord and savior
when they
deny the changes to scripture
i think it's not it's not a salvation
issue
i think it's a sin issue it's a strong
delusion
and um
i think that's really important now why
do i say that what what was i thinking
about well i was thinking about
if one
i think of the gospel being preached to
all nations right
and now people across the earth from the
most part in many countries and many
lands are hearing the gospel they're not
reading the gospel because they're
illiterate
in the western world most of us can read
but if you go into
many parts of the world
illiteracy is high
so
they have a relationship with jesus
christ if they have heard the gospel
right
if they've surrendered their life to
jesus
and
they can't see the change in scripture
but they might be able to hear them
right
if someone is reading the bible to them
they might have a piercing in their
heart
but they may not know
um
my point is i think that for those who
don't see the changes and justify the
perversions
i think what's important is to ask
what do these verses mean
well first and foremost i think it's
important to make sure that they know
who jesus is
and then to have them explain
what these verses are
um
because i can't believe that people
who are professing faith in jesus christ
can embrace what's written in scripture
now
as truth
i don't get it
and it's something i really struggle
with and my listeners you know this i
really grapple with this
and i at different times i think i've
said well i just don't think it's
possible they can be born again but you
know i do think that they can be born
again
but i think that they are
deceived
and as christians we can be deceived
right i mean i think there are times
when i've been deceived
you've probably been deceived
and then by the grace of god he leads us
in in truth and and he brings us out of
of a
believing a lie and he shows us what the
truth is but
with the scripture changes are so
evident you know
i mean like i said the grammar errors
and the nonsense verses speak for
themselves
that the bible's been tampered with
but
again i would ask for those if you guys
been sticking around i want answers i
want i want bible scholars to tell me
what these scripture verses mean what
you think it means i want you to to
explain to me how the bible could be a
um
considered a noteworthy
a noteworthy
piece of literature
with grammar errors and nonsense verses
you know what i'm saying
because from what we're looking at right
here it's not
and
that's the truth
so i'm gonna see what you guys are
saying out here are you guys still here
with me let's see
so i'm gonna go back you guys are
saying a lot here
so friends you know what
i have said in my um in my even my i put
up a video about
um christianity in the government
a video that i put together in 2016. i
just uploaded it to this channel
and um i was really listening to it
today and i did mention that video for
people to go check out anthony patch
and his
videos that he's done on quantum
computing
um
there was a time when i felt like he i
was recommending him
i have since really kind of stopped
because i haven't seen him
warn
the church about the bible changes
and i find that troubling like he's more
concerned with
how this is being done
versus the fact that the bible's being
changed and
um
i can't get my brain rapture on that
because yes i want to know how it's
happening
curious minds want to know
but i think it's more important to warn
the church
that the bible is under attack and
changing
um
and and i haven't seen him do that now
mind you he might have maybe he's come
out and has done whole videos on it on
the bible changing i don't know because
i don't follow him anymore
so
anyway friends no these verses i'm
sharing with you are the king james
bible
so
yep it is possible they do not have a
love for the truth
yeah it's just so interesting um
yeah ginger girl says she she believes
it's really important for me to stay
humble even though i see that some
someone else doesn't everything i see is
because god by his mercy has allowed me
to see
well that is true
that is true and in the scripture verses
that we were sharing today
i want
i mean this is just a small fraction of
them right i mean i could have picked
from any number of screenshots that i
have
but i want
i want answers
because i think that
i know they're not going to be able to
give the right answers
but i kind of i i
well i guess what i want them to do is i
want to see people kind of swarm
i want to see how they justify the
madness
in the bible
i want to know why they can't believe in
the supernatural today
because i think that's also a stumbling
block for them they do not believe in
the supernatural and they for whatever
reason believe that the bible is gonna
is jesus or that the bible will never
fade away
and i'm like okay go go go throw your
bible in your pool
go throw your bible in the in
put it through your your your uh your um
washer or your dryer or not your dryer
just put in your bathtub fill it with
water and let me know
because or put it in the fireplace and
start a fire
because your bible is not going to last
forever
it's
made of elements from this world and
this and what's happening is that we're
seeing things change on a molecular
level
everywhere things are dissolving
and it's crazy it's really really crazy
lighting signs and wonders
friends i think this is enough i think
i'm not going to take collins right now
um
because i want to leave it on this i
want people to
i'm hoping that this video will get into
the hands of
many
many you see many you don't see
and that those who don't see will hear
my real desire
to have you explain
what these verses mean
and i don't want you to go look up the
new king james bible or the bible or or
niv or
because seriously
we should all be able to read any verse
in scripture and know what it's saying
but the verses i just shared with you
their
speak for themselves so please i would
like to hear from people who are
debunking the bible changes
to take a look at these and
give answers stop talking about that the
fact that you remember the wolf being in
isaiah 11 6. that's fine
i
you know what okay so you believe that
but what about these other verses here
and this is just again a fraction
because there are changes on every
single page of the bible
and i'm talking about more than one
they're more than one change in one
verse
one verse
so please i beg of you and i implore you
to
engage with me
and
let's talk about this or
do your own video
and talk about these verses that i'm
presenting right here
and tell the world
what you think that they mean
i beg of you
because
these are troubling verses
and
i don't think you can explain them
and i think that those who don't see i
think you need to have a reckoning
you need
whatever fear you have you need to lay
it at his feet you need to lay it at the
feet of jesus
and tell him this scares you and be
honest because we've all had to do it
and to beg for understanding
and mercy
because that's what the scripture
changes have done for me
it's completely rocked my world
and it's been
a crazy five years
almost five years for me
so anyway friends i love you so much i'm
so glad that you guys are awake those
who are here thank you so much thank you
for your prayers
um
you know
oh breeder says it
they think that mocking those who see as
part of it gaslighting maybe that's too
narcissistic
um
yeah i think that the issue is instead
of
responding to the scripture changes i've
had people
um ask me
some other question like they want to
divert the conversation
and they won't answer my question
and i've tried to pull back people back
and say wait a minute i don't want to
talk about that i don't want to talk
about
that
i ask you a question and i really want
an answer
and every time i've done that
with those who don't see i get
if it's on the phone a long silence
if it's in person i get a blank look
literally
it's the weirdest thing ever
so then
and then what we've seen with those in
the christian community and there are
youtube channels
when you watch them no names
there is a
um a mocking spirit
right
now some would say you're mocking the
bible changes well yeah yeah
when i laugh at them
when i call them out and say this is
disgusting
yeah
i do say that
because i'm
angry that the wicked one has perverted
scripture so
um
and my sarcasm that comes out
it really is more like gosh if i'm not
sarcastic about it i'm going to throw my
bible across the room
or i'm going to go ahead and cry
because it's so crazy
but this is the times that we're in so i
think you guys get it i'm going to leave
it at this i'm i don't want to keep
rambling i know i appreciate your time
being with me tonight and sticking
around
and um would love to hear your thoughts
about the scriptures that i shared with
you so father be with us
tonight god i know that these verses
that i shared tonight are troubling and
these are just a sample of them lord of
changes we see the scripture that are
absolutely
absolutely insane
i pray that
for those who are hearing this for the
first time i pray that you would bless
them with peace
bless all of us with peace lord we
really need it but for those who are
waking up to these changes i pray that
you would be gracious towards them
that you would pour out your love upon
them lord that you give them the courage
that they need
to examine this lord
to search the truth out with you
to spend time with you
to consult you
to cry out to you lord
and i pray that you reveal truth to them
i pray that you give us all answers lord
we want more wisdom and knowledge and
discernment in this hour
we thank you for
the hope that you give to us lord
and your peace that surpasses all
understanding
we're so grateful god i pray your
blessing upon all of my listeners i pray
great encouragement lord in favor over
each of them and i pray that miracles
would come upon them lord i pray
answered prayer would be theirs
provision from heaven lord and i pray
that they will begin to see the
the hearts of their children the hearts
of their loved ones
turn to you lord i i pray that we will
begin to see the salvation of our family
members lord and of our loved ones
we pray for this lord that more people
would enter into your kingdom with great
joy and praise and thanksgiving for your
glory and your praise
in jesus name hallelujah all right
everybody i want to go it's been great
hanging out with you tonight
and i love you all in jesus name let me
know what you guys think about these
verses
again you're asking um
it's a kjv bible
that i'm showing everyone tonight
the kjv bible
all right everybody god bless you all
thank you for being here and we'll get
together soon
in jesus name hallelujah